Before using the modeler, first import a modeler.
After importing the modeler, you need to change the modeler to a vertical position to wear the costume.
The position of the modeler can be changed by inserting the action in the viewport folder.
Click on the modeler, double-click the folder, view all costumes, and select the costume you need.
If you need a female jacket, you can find the corresponding Women Jacket folder.
After opening the camera, you can see the style chart at the bottom.
After the camera style chart, you can import the costume according to your needs.
After importing, you can open the simulation, the costume will be worn on the virtual modeler.
You can modify the modeling costume according to your needs.